id	status	reporter_name	description
1	PENDING	Thanu	Injured Spotted Deer Near Roadside ? A spotted deer was seen injured near the roadside close to the Guindy National Park entrance in Chennai around 6:30 PM. The animal appeared to have a leg injury and was unable to walk properly. Several people were nearby, and the deer seemed frightened. Immediate assistance from the wildlife rescue team may be required to safely relocate and treat the animal.
2	PENDING	Citizen Tester	Test Wildlife Issue ? This is a test report to verify the Investigate button in the admin dashboard.
